<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 13:55:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Guess The Output of this Code</title>
      <link>/guess-the-output-of-this-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 13:55:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guess-the-output-of-this-code/</guid>
      <description>Over the time that I have been working with ServiceNow I have discovered several interesting quirks about the behavior of the code. Some of them kept me wondering for a while, others made me giggle. I want to share one of them with you, that I have discovered recently with Dylan, while debugging one of our applications, that left us with one question: Why does it work like that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Good, the Bad, and the Ugly About ServiceNow from a Developer&#39;s Perspective</title>
      <link>/the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly-about-servicenow-from-a-developers-perspective/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly-about-servicenow-from-a-developers-perspective/</guid>
      <description>Over the years, the concept of &amp;ldquo;platform&amp;rdquo; has been growing and become one of the main topics regarding IT Service Management. ServiceNow is one company in particular that has become a big thing in this space. Sure, the list of companies using the ServiceNow platform is impressive, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t show how many people are actually using or familiar with the platform. What really brought this to my attention is when I mention ServiceNow while talking to people working in big companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Not Fail Your ServiceNow Certification Exam</title>
      <link>/how-to-not-fail-your-servicenow-certification-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-to-not-fail-your-servicenow-certification-exam/</guid>
      <description>Want a foolproof plan to guarantee success on your ServiceNow Certification Exam? Well, this isn’t it, but it’s as close as I can get! I’m not offering any guarantees, but what I can offer is a guide which has been proven successful for both myself and the rest of my team. By the end of reading this post my goal is to have you feeling prepared and confident to go out and crush your ServiceNow certification exam!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>